(Penny:)Oh, my God,
Sheldon the genius is jealous of Leonard.
(Sheldon:)I'm not jealous.
(Sheldon:)I'm just very unhappy that good things are
happening for him and not happening for me.
(Penny:)Sweetie, this is a natural thing to feel.
(Penny:)Just because good things
are happening to Leonard...
(Penny:)...doesn't take anything away from you.
Let me tell you a story.
(Penny:)There was a girl who worked
at the Cheesecake Factory...
...and she wasn't good at herjob.
- It was you.
(Penny:)It wasn't me.
(Penny:)But she was also an actress.
(Penny:)We were both up for the same part
in a toothpaste commercial. She got it.
(Penny:)I was so jealous, but instead of
ripping out her fake blond hair...
You ripped out your own fake blond hair.
(Penny:)I looked her in the eye, smiled and said,
"I'm happy for you."
(Penny:)Because that's what friends do.
(Sheldon:)They lie so they don't look petty.
(Penny:)- Yeah.
- How?
(Penny:)Like this.
(Penny:)I am so happy for you.
(Leonard:)Wow.